MICHELE LISIGNO

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Expressing my *creativity* is my lifeblood and technology is my greatest passion. I have been attracted to it since I was a child, developing over the years a study and research methodology to keep knowledge updated and quickly learn new ones.

I would like to make a valuable contribution to a company where I can work towards continuous improvement by sharing my skills and my values.

PERSONAL INFO

- Morbegno 03/12/1991
- +39 324 0813121
- Piuro, Italy

LANGUAGES

Italian - Native language English - Excellent written and spoken French - Basic knowledge

ATTITUDE

Respectful - Loyal - Passionate Determined - Eager to learn Creative - Positive - Professional **Problem Solving** Thinking out of the box









EXPERIENCE

JR. FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

January 2021 - July 2021 | Boolean Careers

Full-time immersion in the latest web development technologies, creating and testing many application mockups on both frontend and backend side from the study of functionalities to production.

WEB DESIGNER - UI/UX DESIGNER

May 2019 - December 2020 | ArteGrafica Studio

Creation of many responsive websites design studying and testing the best layouts solutions for offer our users the best experience. Creation of others graphic products like logos, magazines, video editing and 3D renderings. Acquiring a huge sensitivity to style and attention to details.

EXECUTIVE CHEF - THAILAND

February 2014 - April 2019 | BKK, Chang Mai, Koh Samui I leaded the Link Cuisine & Lounge, managing 4 restaurants. Despite being in a distant environment, I developed important skills that still come in handy today:

Take on many responsibilities - Relate to clients-colleagues Find solutions quickly and under pressure Managing deadlines - Managing budgets - Be organised.

CHEF - AUSTRALIA February 2012 - May 2013 | Sydney Vacanza Pizzeria and at Hux Dining. During this time I have improved my English a lot.

SECOND CHEF July 2010 - January 2012 | Chiavenna, Italy | La Villa Restaurant

ASSISTANT CHEF Summer 2009 - 2008 - 2007 - 2006 Chiavenna, Madesimo, Messina, Piuro.

EDUCATION

MASTER NODE.JS - REACT.JS DEVELOPER Zero To Mastery Academy | July 2021 - Agoust 2021

MASTER FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER Boolean Careers | January 2021 - July 2021 Click here to check the certificate

TECHNOLOGIES KNOWLEDGE

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT













GRAPHIC DESIGN







InDesign







Final Cut









MySQL





BACKEND DEVELOPMENT



MongoDB